They say behind every successful man is
a strong woman, and I need to stop and
give a shout-out to my rock and [music]
the thing that keeps going.
Y'all see me online doing all these
amazing things, but what you don't know
is this woman here works just as hard as
I do, probably harder. Um and she's been
dragging me along for the last 3 years 6
months and
I just wanted to give a shout-out to
Alex. How long have we been together,
baby?
>> Almost 4 years.
>> Have we been around the world?
>> Yep.
>> Where are we now?
>> We're going to tell.
>> Are you with me [music] through thick?
>> Yep.
>> And thin?
>> Good and bad?
>> Yep.
>> Are you tired?
>> [music]
>> Are you hungry?
>> No.
>> Are you ever going to leave me?
No.
>> I love you so much and I just wanted to
stop and give credit where credit is
due.
>> Mhm.
>> Alex is a champion.